All pirates searching for the treasure One Piece must brave the second half of the Grand Line.
These wild and dangerous seas are known as the New World.
Gold Roger and his crew were the only men to ever chart these waters and learn all the secrets they held.
For the rest of the pirates of the world, this has proven to be the end of the road, a graveyard of dreams.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body became rubber after eating the gum gum fruit, sets sail into the New World with his faithful crew.
I'm going to be the king of the pirates!
During their journey to the New World, Luffy and his crew arrive on Fishman Island, which is located 10,000 meters below sea level.
The Fishman Pirates, led by Hordy Jones and assisted by Vander Decken, plot to overthrow King Neptune.
It's not long before the Straw Hats get pulled into the conflict and find themselves in the midst of an all-out war.
If you want to take my life, then I am powerless to stop you!
But no one else should have to suffer!
I won't let you harm this kingdom!
I will protect it with my life!
So come get me, you monster!
Damn it, weepy Hoshi! I told you to stay where I can protect you!
I'll show you what happens to traitors, Vander Decken. But I do admit I like this idea of yours.
I can't believe I'm letting you save the girl! You better not let us down! Don't hold anything back, Luffy!
Here I go!
Hurry up, Luffy! Shira Hoshi's life in jeopardy!
Whoa! What's it doing?
It's leaving! Look! And Noah's not headed toward the island anymore!
The Princess is leading it away from us! It won't crash into us after all!
Don't let it hit you!
Swim faster!
Where do you think you're going? You know you can't run away, don't you? There is no escape!
If I'm going to steer the Noah clear of the bubble, then I have to swim as far out to sea as I can!
The bubble will surely break if it takes any more damage!
But the main entrance is too far away!
No, wait! I believe Luffy and his friends were the last ones to leave the Ryugu Palace!
If that's the case, perhaps the gateway is still open!
Oh no! Isn't there some way to help instead of just standing here?!
What does Vander Decken have to gain from this anyway?!
Leave our princess alone, you monster!
It's not Shira Hoshi's fault! She doesn't deserve to die for this!
Horny's climbing out of the ship too?!
That can't be good! What if he attacks her again?!
There's no one to protect her! She can't fight him!
Decken, you filthy traitor! Have you lost your damned mind?!
This is far from over! I can make use of that madman!
Keep your wits about you, Luffy!
Fishmen are far stronger than humans in the water! Do not forget that!
Uh-huh!
I can't throw Luffy too hard or he'll break through the bubble and go flying out to sea!
So I'm gonna have to do it extra carefully!
With exactly the right amount of force!
Now, Sanji!
Arme de lair assault!
Come shoot!
This thing's pretty big!
I guess I'm between the bubbles now?
Wait, Horty's still under the bubble.
We can't stop this thing, but if we can slow it down, even just a little, maybe she can get away!
Come on! Don't let it catch her!
Hurry, Princess! We'll try to slow it down. You get somewhere safe!
Damn it! It's too heavy!
Are they crazy? My people!
Who came up with that plan? No matter how hard they pull, that ship will never move an inch.
Why don't I just put you out of your misery?
Come on! Back off!
I can't lose!
Aren't you worthless scum? You're the reason humans look down on our entire race.
My kingdom has no place for sentimental weaklings like you!
If your pride as fishmen means nothing to you, then your pathetic lives mean nothing to me!
You soiled the name of our proud race. This is the fate you deserve.
Damn it, Horty!
We're so hurry, your majesty! Just swim away! You're hurrying me!
I mustn't stop now!
I was right! The entrance to the palace is still open!
Just hang in there, buddy! Horty! I'll cut you out!
She made it up to the gate!
She's swimming out to sea!
The Noah's still on her tail!
You can do it, Princess!
PJ Sumpets!
It's going up!
Whoa!
I can't steer this thing!
goat six
Poor, feeble humans. Must be inconvenient.
You all act so high and mighty when you're safe on land.
But here in the water, you're not even a match for the smallest fish man child.
A man is only as strong as he is at his weakest, I'm afraid.
You might be powerful up on the island, but you're in my territory now.
Shut up and fight me!
You don't listen very well, do you?
We're not on the ground anymore, kid.
You think you can keep up while you're being tossed around in that bubble?
I hate to break it to you, but if you're worried about Shirahoshi, you're gonna be long dead before that ship hits her.
Speaking of the princess, she did me a favor going out to sea.
You can send her a thank you note from your watery grave!
Shark arrows!
How's that devil fruit power of yours working out by the way? How did you think this would go?
How arrogant to think you had a chance in the sea.
Perhaps you understand at last.
In the bitter end, you humans will finally see that you're unfit to rule this world.
A lesson learned far too late, I'm afraid.
Pathetic. Can't even breathe.
All the fools who enter these waters will pay a high price for their arrogance.
It's far too late now to beg for mercy!
But you're not even capable of that anymore, are you?
Truly such a miserable creature! Now prepare to rot in hell!
Now prepare to rot in hell!
Back for more, are you?
Are you alright? Speak to me, Luffy!
Hey, it's you!
Too bad that kind gesture was in vain.
Because I'm not about to let you get away.
Now say goodbye!
You get away. Now say goodbye!
Tch-he-he-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
Ha, ha, ha, ha.
Paul! Paul!
We can't stop this thing, but if we can slow it down even just a little, maybe she can get away!
Come on! Don't let it catch her!
Hurry, Princess! We'll try to slow it down! You get somewhere safe!
This isn't enough. If I want to save the people of my kingdom, I have to lure the Noah far away from the island!
As far as I possibly can!
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha! I almost forgot to ask Shira Hoshi!
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha!
How does freedom feel? After ten years, you're no longer protected by the cold stone walls of the hardshell tower!
And now it's time for you to bleed to death, my darling. That is, unless you'd rather be crushed by the massive weight of the Noah!
But one teeny tiny little magic word can spare you this dread fate, and that's yes!
Simply under that one word and your troubles will be over!
I'm deeply sorry, Sir Deccan, but I simply can't do that!
Why must you refuse to marry me?!
Because you're not my type!
I see.
I do hell with you!
Die today! And live for eternity! Deep within my poor, miserable heart! Then you'll be mine! Figuratively at least!
You need to learn how to treat a lady! Or anybody for that matter!
Shira Hoshi is our baby sister! We will never let you lay a hand on her! Not ever!
You came to save me! And Ho is here as well! Thank you!
Oh! Well, hello, brothers-in-law!
We are not your family!
Oh, brothers! Some of our people attempted to save me, but then they were...
Now's not the time for tears, Shira Hoshi!
Oh, please don't get mad at me!
I said don't cry!
Focus, you two! Father told us that we shouldn't let any harm come to the Noah Solatino!
We have to find a way to get it safely back to the sea floor without letting it hit anything along the way!
Look out!
Listen! We need you to mumble your way around the underwater mountains and dritches!
And don't rock the boat, baby!
But there are so many obstacles! Where should I go?
Up there! The path should be a lot clearer that way!
All right, I'll go!
He won't get away from me, Fasola!
You will never escape, my love!
It's as hopeless as you trying to escape the hot pursuit of the Noah!
I'll chase after you as long as I have to, my beautiful bride!
Good thing you showed up! Thanks a lot!
But you got hurt pretty bad back there, are you okay?
My pain means nothing when so many soldiers, citizens, and royal family members were attacked.
Even my sister Shira Hoshi's trying her best to save the Ryugu Kingdom, despite the injury she suffered.
So you see, there simply isn't time for me to sit back and lick my wounds!
Well in that case, can I ask you a favor?
Forgive me, but there's no time for that either!
Furfolk like them are supposed to be the fastest swimmers in the whole world!
But with my new power, I can swim circles around them!
Not again!
Now, Shark Slicer!
Okay, do not let us get hit by that!
Perhaps I'll slice you into nice fillets, then I can feed your flesh to the little fishes!
A prince of the Ryugu Kingdom and a pirate who's worth 400 million!
They're sure to enjoy that meal!
Yeah!
Regardless of where his power comes from, his speed is undeniable!
Hold on tightly, Straw Hat!
He's cutting through stuff just like Zoro! This is crazy!
You should save your admiration for later!
No matter which way you cowards go, you can never outswim the blade of my Shark Slicer!
Hoping you'll lose me in this cloud of dust, are you?
Whoa ha ha!
Huh?
What happened?
Hey, we need to get on top of that ship, quick!
Oh no, no!
What happened?
The Noah!
Baa-ho-ho-ho-ho!
Shira-ho-shi!
What happened?
Hey, we need to get on top of that ship, quick!
Damn you, Deccan.
I assume this is the favor you were going to ask before,
but I failed to see the purpose.
It's something Jinbei told me.
But the ship's in a bubble, so it should be okay!
That would make sense.
Deccan is weak to seawater, just like you.
Despite being a fish man, he needs air to move around freely.
It'll be easier for me to fight there,
and I'm about ready to kick the crap out of Hordy
and that weirdo who likes to throw stuff.
Besides, I promised we'd be Hoshi when we left the tower.
I'm supposed to make sure she's safe.
It seems we are of one mind.
And just like our father, your sons will become noble warriors.
With all of our strength,
we will protect Shira Hoshi in body and spirit alike.
I made the same promise.
Yet we allowed ourselves to be bested by a scoundrel
who draws his power from some drug.
It seems I've failed to keep my word to our late mother.
I also regret being suspicious of you at first.
Eh, it's no big deal. Let's head to the deck.
I've got business there too.
What is this?
I can eliminate Straw at any time.
But there's another issue I need to take care of
that simply cannot wait any longer.
What are you waiting for? Come on!
No. We must be cautious.
What do you mean, no?
He's up to something.
More than that, we must be prepared for another encounter underwater.
Clearly our prior approach was inadequate.
So what do we do?
I have an idea.
Please, come on! Higher!
You've lived with my markmark curse long enough
to know you can't escape.
And unlike those axes your little tower protected you from,
there's nothing in this wide world
that could stop the Noah from crushing you to itty bitty bits.
Baa-ho-ho-ho-ho-ho-ho-ho!
Goodness, if it isn't horny, Jones!
Jones say whatever happened to Neptune dead maybe by the way I'm using the
Noah to torture Shirahoshi as we speak a genius idea on my part don't you think
brother it's not bad but I think I've got an even better idea do you now well
let's hear it actually it's better if I show you
if you died what would become of this ship
well Deccan
party's unexpected assault on Deccan threatens to destroy all of Fishman Island yet even as
impending doom looms in the sky above them the straw hats continue their struggle at the bottom
of the sea the appearance of a new ally gives Luffy a chance to protect Shirahoshi but it will take
much more than that to save the rest of the island on the next one piece the fierce fight begins
luffy versus horde I'm gonna be king of the pirates